all right so we're starting the YouTube
channel on 1111 for the 1111 challenge
so we started off with 1100 bucks I
think it was like about a month ago and
right now the account is currently
sitting at
$6,300 so this is where we took last
week's trade which gave us a total
profit of about 3,000 no
2,873 we haven't taken any trades in
about a week and then today is Tuesday
and I still haven't taken the trades but
I did take a trade on my personal
account which is a trade that I sent out
in telegram Instagram everywhere and on
that trade right now I'm currently up
about
$133,000 so we're just up about 20K pop
a little clip of that right now and
we're here right now with Steve we got
Steve over
there way free gas so we're probably
already about 3 hours into the whole
event because we pulled up at 8:30 it
was a little bit chaotic at the
beginning but we're already giving away
gas and we're about to finish wrapping
up in about another hour or two but
we're going to give you guys some trade
ideas in a little bit to see what other
trades we could get so I missed the
first trade but let's see if we can get
the second one so check it so let's do a
trade update on the 1111 Challenge on
the only trade that I took from December
17th to December 23rd which there was
only one trade idea that I sent in my
free telegram where I gave the
pre-analysis and then I also entered the
trade once even though I scaled in two
times on a trade idea I only entered the
trade one time so let me show you guys
this is GBP cat so this is the only
trade that I took on December 20th 2023
you guys can see it down here
which is a very clean break and retest
of The Head and Shoulders we identified
this right here to be our left this to
be our head and then this right here to
be our right shoulder so then once we
broke the neckline of The Head and
Shoulders we simply waited for the
retest of the neckline along with a
round psychological level
7500 and once we got the retest of the
area of Interest round psychological
level we also have a retest of the EMA
so we have three very strong Confluence
to take this trade and I simply went
onto the low lower time frames and
waited for my entry signal you can see
right here it's a very clear rejection
bearish engulfing Candlestick Evening
Star formation rejection from the EMA
and the area of Interest simply enter
the trade from this bearish and golfing
Candlestick right here and then we set
and forget and got a total of a 1 to
three risk forward trade SLE so we only
took one trade in this week of December
and in this trade I was risking anywhere
from 7 to $800 where it gave me a to a 1
to3 risk reward where led me to make
about $4 to $5,000 almost which was a
very solid trade setup and I started at
the beginning of this week with $6,300
to then where I closed this week at
$122,000 in profit so now let's see how
we end up next week where I can expect
to take this 12,000 to roughly 20 to
25,000 so let's see what next week has
to bring so it's week four of the 11-11
challenge where I started with
$1,111 and currently right now we are
sitting at
$112,000 and every single trade that I
take I must send in my free Telegram and
that's what we're going to do right now
we're going to break down the trades
that I'm going to be looking for this
week ahead so if you guys come inside oh
yo that thing scares the out of me
every single time I come in here it's my
new house my new office don't mind it
it's literally just getting built so
let's go over the trades that I'm going
to be trading this week where we're
going to potentially take this 12,000 to
maybe 20,000 by the end of the week I
don't know so P up so we're going to
start off the week with AUD CAD so AUD
CAD as of right now what we are waiting
for is for a daily pullback into this
area right here and as of right now we
have had a quick retracement into the
area so technically the trade is already
gone because we already had this
retracement as you can see right now it
is currently December 26th 1:41 a.m. so
pretty much before uh London session
trade happened a little bit before
London session so we kind of missed it
so I'm going to be waiting for now for a
little retracement for Trace to come
back in so we can potentially you know
take another another buy to the upside
next we are looking for is nzd JPY which
is a very simple break retest same exact
thing happened very fast so we kind of
missed the trade so I'm going to be
waiting for any pull back into here to
then buy the trade because it happened
very fast and then next is
gbpnzd which we were waiting for a daily
pullback into this area right here which
this can probably take a couple of days
so as of right now both both of the
trades that we were anticipating
happened fast cuz it's Christmas the day
after Christmas December 26th 2 in the
morning so let's see what happens later
in New York so it is currently Tuesday
Morning 9:13 in the morning so let's
review the trades that I was explaining
last night which one of them actually
played out and one of them is about to
play out currently right now the account
balance remains exactly the same
$1,188 and this is AUD cads analysis
from last night so we were expecting a
pull back into the zone to then wait for
an entry signal to take the trade that's
exactly what we're happening so I'm
going to wait for a rejection right
around the 1 hour time frame so let's
see if we can get some type of bullish
Candlestick to eat this one or some type
of rejection here next is nzd JPY which
exactly what I explained yesterday that
I wanted to happen as you guys can see
nzd JPY happened to Perfection pullback
to retest The Zone if you noticed I drew
this out yesterday and the line followed
it to the Perfection the wick happened
to the perfect point of that okayu
that's crazy so this one we missed it it
actually happened at 4:30 in the morning
or 4:00 in the morning you see that
Candlestick right there happened at 4:00
in the morning so 1 hour after I
actually fell asleep I fell asleep at 3:
and then gvp nzd we're still waiting for
it to make it up so as of right now no
trade just waiting for a cat so we're
going to go eat right now no trades as
of right now the wrap is currently
coming off because of the Christmas
lights that we did you can see right
here all of
the leftovers of the tape from the
Christmas
lights but let's do a little cold
start it sounds like a
jet here winding up I'm sorry
Neighbors
[Music]
all right so trade up there right now so
it is currently 5:00 in the afternoon so
the daily C to is about to close and as
you can see we are currently having a
rejection so it looks pretty good so we
might be able to enter a trade during
London tonight so you guys can see it
right here with a beautiful sunset all
right good morning ladies and gentlemen
so it is currently Wednesday morning I
think I've slept 3 hours off for nothing
Well actually this is the wrong account
for the other account where also
negative as well off for nothing so let
me show you guys so this is currently
right now how we are on the 11-11
challenge as of right now we're down
about 500 bucks this is the trade we're
in so how did I come up with that risk
management right there I simply went to
a position size calculator put the pair
put the account size how much I want to
risk which is 20% of the account and
then
I I got this lot size so yes 20% is a
lot but this is a scaling account so it
doesn't really matter um I'm just
waiting for this to play out I think it
could hold up very nicely we're
retesting the neckline of The Head and
Shoulders retesting the EMA so let's see
let's see what's going to happen now for
now we're just going to set and forget
we got exactly what I was anticipa uh
anticipating yesterday which is a clean
rejection from here I'm just entering at
the retracement the other pair that I
was predicting which is nzd JPY has
pretty much much played out so kind of
missed it and then GBP CAD looks like
it's making its way back up potentially
but it's Wednesday so I don't think
it'll make it all the way back here and
then have a push by Friday so it's like
that about an hour later currently we're
up about $1,000 on the trade so playing
out very nicely and as of now just set
and forget oh oh oh
oh oh oh
oh so market up there right now it is
currently 8:00 at night and you guys can
see that the trade is currently running
beautifully we're creating new higher
highs I have my alarm set up at my
takeprofit which if the trade hits that
point we could probably close at about
maybe $5,000 $4,800 but if we hit my
actual take profit which is going to be
that high right there then we can almost
make $7,000 on this trade which is
pretty solid CU it's played out in under
48 hours so for now we're going to
continue to set and forget all right
guys good morning so again don't mind
this office I hate how it looks right
now we're going to make it a lot better
but the trade has been closed officially
and we're currently sitting at about
$117,000 let me show you guys so this is
currently where we are right now on the
account so we made about 5k on that
trade yesterday and you guys can tell
take profit was so precise that as soon
as it hit the take profit came back into
the entry this is what my Center forget
strategy is about literally shows you
the entries perfectly and the take
profits perfectly I say so as of right
now we can even potentially be looking
for a new entry very soon uh next we
also have nzdjpy which came back to the
area wasn't interested in it because I
was mainly focused on the other trade
and then next is gvp CAD so kind of how
I mentioned it earlier we were waiting
for it to make it all the way back up
into this area it kind of started having
momentum for that but now it's starting
to head back to the downside so for now
my only priority is going to be adding a
position on AUD C at the beginning of
this week we started the challenge with
about $112,000 where I only took one
trade this week you guys saw that me
document everything when it comes to AUD
CAD entered the trade we're in a little
bit of drw down and then we saw the
trade hit take profit thousands of
Traders caught this trade alongside with
me everything was literally copied to
Perfection then we closed off the week
at about 16 almost $177,000 where I was
risking anywhere from $8 to $900 on this
trade which gave us about the 5K I was
going low risk because I was being
conservative cuz I'm only looking to
take at least one two trades a week Max
so you guys are seeing how set FR
strategy is literally happening week
after week after week after the week
I've been doing this challenge now for a
month and a half and I have won every
single trade so you guys have seen with
s and forget how I've won every single
trade for the last month on this account
I haven't lost one single trade and
everything is documented here live and
on telegram Instagram everywhere so if
you want to know more about what set and
forget is and how I use it to make these
profits every single week just click the
link in the description below I have a
video there for you that explains exact
what set and forget is and how thousands
of my students are making anywhere from
,000 to $1,500 a week as a beginner set
and forget Trader so you want to know
more about s and forget click the link
in the description below and I'll see
you guys in the next video